Guide to the Violet Hunt papers, 1858-1962.
Hunt, Violet papers, 1858-1962.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Violet Hunt papers, 1858-1962.
4607
Violet Hunt 1862-1942.
9.7 c.f.
Correspondence, manuscripts, diaries, estate records and documents, financial records and account books, drawings, photographs, research notes, publishing correspondence, clippings.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Correspondence, manuscripts, diaries, estate records and documents, financial records and account books, drawings, photographs, research notes, publishing correspondence, clippings, book reviews, and other papers of Violet Hunt, with particular reference to her family and social relations, her publishing career, and to her book The Wife of Rossetti. Includes genealogies and others records relating to the Hunt and Hueffer families, three diaries (1914, 1918, 1919), and an address book.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
British author, biographer.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Correspondence, manuscripts, diaries, estate records and documents, financial records and account books, drawings, photographs, research notes, publishing correspondence, clippings, book reviews, and other papers of Violet Hunt, with particular reference to her family and social relations, her publishing career, and to her book The Wife of Rossetti. Includes genealogies and others records relating to the Hunt and Hueffer families, three diaries (1914, 1918, 1919), and an address book.
Major correspondents and subjects include Ford Madox (Hueffer) Ford, Francis Hueffer, Ford Madox Brown, Richard Garnett, Rebecca West, Elizabeth Siddall Rossetti, Christina Rossetti, Charles Algernon Swinburne, Edward Coley Burne-Jones, John Ruskin, Dante Gabriel Rossetti, and Radclyffe Hall.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Hunt, Violet,1862-1942.; Brown, Ford Madox.; Burne-Jones, Edward Coley, 1833-1898.; Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939.; Hall, Radclyffe, 1886-1943.; Hueffer family.; Hueffer, Francis, 1843-1889.; Hunt family.; Hunt, Violet, 1862-1942.; Rossetti, Christina Georgina, 1830-1894.; Rossetti, Dante Gabriel, 1828-1882.; Ruskin, John, 1819-1900.; Siddall, Elizabeth.; Swinburne, Charles Algernon, 1837-1909.; Waugh, Evelyn, 1903-1966.; West, Rebecca,
Subjects:
Authors, English--20th century.; Women and literature.; British literature--20th century.; Genealogies.
Places:
Related collection: Ford Madox Ford papers, #4605.
Form and Genre Terms:
Photographs.; Diaries.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Family
Boxes 1-5
Series II. Correspondence
Boxes 6-10, 24, 26
Series III. Diaries
Boxes 10-12, 24, 27
Series IV. Manuscripts
Boxes 12-18, 25, 26
Series V. Documents - Miscellaneous Documents, By Individual
Boxes 18, 25, 26
Series VI. Miscellaneous
Boxes 18, 24, 27
Series VII. Photographs
Boxes 19, 20
Series VIII. Printed Material
Box 21
Series IX. Drawings
Boxes 23-26
Series X. Research Material - Research Notes
Box 26
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Family
  - 1. Hunt family (Raine/Peacock/Hunt)
    - a. Correspondence
      - i. Alfred William Hunt to and from Margaret Raine Hunt
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [n.d.] (Box 1, Folder 1-a)
          AL [frag.] S [init.] to Alfred Hunt
          [n.p.] ...care of yourself and don't/get
          2 ll.
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [n.d.] (Box 1, Folder 1-b)
          ALS [init.] to Alfred Hunt
          [n.p.] My dearest Alfred It seems very long to be without/hearing from you
          With ALS from Violet Hunt to Alfred Hunt, [n.d.], appended to Margaret Hunt's letter.
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Sunday [n.d.] (Box 1, Folder 1-c)
          [n.p.] My dearest Alfred Your sister has sent her letter/and papers
          3 ll.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Sunday afternoon [n.d.] (Box 1, Folder 1-d)
          ALS [init.] to Margaret Raine Hunt
          [n.p.] I have just got your letter/and
          4 ll.
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 1, Folder 1-e)
          Dusseldorf My own darling Alfred I get so very uneasy/about you
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Wednesday [n.d.] (Box 1, Folder 1-f)
          Graefrath My own darling Alfred It seems so selfish/of me
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Friday [n.d.] (Box 1, Folder 1-g)
          AL [frag.] to Alfred Hunt
          Graefrath My own darling Alfred I arrived here quite/safely this afternoon.
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Aug. 27, 1858 [written on envelope] (Box 1, Folder 2-a)
          AL to Alfred Hunt
          Friday morning [n.d.] [n.p.] I kept this/ to see if there was a letter
          1 l. + 1
          With envelope.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- 1859-1867 (Box 1, Folder 2-b)
          Four empty envelopes addressed to Margaret Raine Hunt
          4 ll. Two addressed to Miss Raine and two to Mrs. Hunt.
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Oct. 2 [1858] (Box 1, Folder 2-c)
          [n.p.] My dearest Alfred I was so/much disappointed
          4 ll. + 1
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-d)
          [n.p.] My own darling Margaret I am oppressed with/a fear
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Jan. 5, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-e)
          Liverpool My dearest Margaret No letter this morning
          2 ll. + 1
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Jan. 8, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-f)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Your letter came all right/by the next post
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Jan. 11, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-g)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Your letter is very kind/yet I could almost quarrel/
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Feb. 17, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-h)
          Conway My dearest Margaret You say nothing about Grae/frath in this mornings letter
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Mar. 5, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-i)
          AL [frag.] to Margaret Raine Hunt
          [n.p.] ...would be utterly useless/to paint from
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Mar. 27, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-j)
          [Capel Curig] My own dearest Margaret You ingenious little woman,
          4 ll. + 1.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 5, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-k)
          Liverpool My own dearest Margaret I am sure that I have/done right in not sending that/ picture
          3 ll. + 1
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 6, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 2-l)
          Liverpool My dearest M. To think of scolding me
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 8, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-a)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I think you ought to/go to Grafrath as soon as possible
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 11, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-b)
          [Darlington] My dearest M. Don't be vexed/ with my letter
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 12, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-c)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret My mother is not really/ better
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 15, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-d)
          [Liverpool] My own dearest Margaret I have almost made up my mind
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 16, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-e)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Even now I cannot/ be positive about Monday/or Wednesday
          2 ll. + 2 + 1
          With ALS from James Wyatt to A.W. Hunt, dated April 15, 1859.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 17, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-f)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Would you address as/usual to the Post Office
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 19, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-g)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I don't know what kind/of a letter this morning will/bring me
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 21, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-h)
          [Liverpool] My dearest M I've got a Murray/ and a passport
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [May 19, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-i)
          [n.p.] My dearest Margaret I have just a quarter/of an hour before the steamer/comes
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [May 25, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-j)
          [n.p.] My darling Alfred. I was so delighted the/ Hofrath
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [May 27, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-k)
          [Graefrath] My darling Alfred - I have not written to/S.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- July 3, [1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-l)
          Lucerne My dearest Margaret I am sadly out of love
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [July 26, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 3-m)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred I was delighted to receive/your letter
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Aug. 2, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-a)
          [Lucerne] My darling Margaret I am beginning to forget/what you are like--I sadly want
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Aug. 2, 1859 (Box 1, Folder 4-b)
          Envelope addressed to Alfred Hunt
          [Dusseldorf]
          1 l.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Aug. 4, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-c)
          Lucerne My sweetest Margaret I am counting the days now--and/you will have no difficulty
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Aug. 17, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-d)
          [Darlington] My darling Margaret My last letter from this/place was not nice
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Aug. 18, [1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-e)
          Darlington My dearest Margaret I have had an afternoon's/work -- but without a glimpse of the sun
          Letter is continued on August 19 and August 20.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Aug. 21, [1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-f)
          [Darlington] My own sweetest Margaret I am sorry to have disappointed/you
          With ALS from J. Plint to Alfred Hunt, dated August 9, 1859; and AL [frag. ] S from Maria Hunt to Alfred Hunt, [1959].
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Aug. 27, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-g)
          [Darlington] My darling Margaret We are going to have a/soft week, says Mr. Ward
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Aug. 28, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-h)
          [Darlington] My darling Margaret I have just been reading over/an old letter of yours
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Aug. 30, [1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-i)
          ALS to Margaret Raine Hunt
          [Darlington] My own dearest Margaret Even a wet day (which I/would rather not think of) would be/more endurable
          Letter finished on August 31.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Sept. 1, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-j)
          [Darlington] My darling Margaret For goodness sake let's return/to the old scale?
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Sept. 2, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-k)
          [Darlington] My darling Margaret Today was such a sulky/day in every way
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Sept. 8, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-l)
          [Darlington] My dearest Margaret I am not better but the/contrary -- I thought of moving to Durham
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 1, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 4-m)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Excuse a short letter --/I got here safe and well
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 2, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-a)
          [Liverpool] My own darling Margaret I am left by myself this/morning -- and should feel very dull/ indeed
          2 ll. + 3 + 1
          With AL [frag.] from Margaret Raine Hunt to [?], [n.d.].
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 6, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-b)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Don't let W.G. think of/such a thing as sending me
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 8, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-c)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret My descent upon Mr. Laurence was successful
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 10, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-d)
          [Liverpool] My own darling Margaret Nothing new -- I felt as if/I could not live any longer
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 11, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-e)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Do you wish to make me forget myself
          Letter finished on October 12.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 14, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-f)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I am in a state/of doubt and vexation
          With ALS from J.N. Parsons to Alfred Hunt, dated October 12, 1859.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 18, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-g)
          [Liverpool] My dearest M You must excuse a very/poor letter again today
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 28, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-h)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret It is so dull and dark that/I can do no work today
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Nov. 1, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-i)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I enclose Mr. Lucas' letter/with extract from Dublin Univ. Mag.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Nov. 5, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-j)
          AL [frag.] S to Margaret Raine Hunt
          [Liverpool] ...a rather busy third day./I know darling I am very thankful to/you
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Nov. 23, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-k)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I got your letter on Monday -- it made/me so ashamed of the fact
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Dec. 4, [1859] (Box 1, Folder 5-l)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I posted a letter for you this afternoon --/send me word whether it was not overweight.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Dec. 5, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 6-a)
          [n.p.] My darling Margaret There was no letter for me this/morning -- I suppose you wait until you
          4 ll. + 2 + 1
          With two notes to Miss Raine.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Dec. 8, 1859] (Box 1, Folder 6-b)
          Liverpool My dearest Margaret I was the least little bit surprised
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Dec. 19, [1859] (Box 1, Folder 6-c)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I received your note enclosed in/a note from your mother
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Dec. 22, [1859] (Box 1, Folder 6-d)
          [n.p.] My dearest Margaret Your last letter was delightful/but as my mother is sitting
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Jan. 11, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-e)
          [n.p.] My dearest Alfred - You are altogether wrong/about the lineup.
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Jan. 13, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-f)
          [n.p.] My own dear love - I really am very well indeed
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Jan. 23, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-g)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred - I was quite astonished/to receive a letter
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Jan. 27, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-h)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred - I do so wish I could see/your picture
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Jan. 29, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-i)
          [Graefrath] My own darling Alfred. It seems such a long/time since I have written
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Feb. 12 [1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-j)
          Graefrath My own dearest Alfred - I am not conscious of any/irregularity
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Feb. 22, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-k)
          [n.p.] My own dear treasure Alfred - I am waiting so anxiously for
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Friday [March 13, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-l)
          Graefrath My own darling Alfred. I have lots to tell you so/I begin my letter
          With envelope dated March 13, 1860.
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Apr. 10, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-m)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret You must please excuse
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [May 6, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-n)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred - I would have written/sooner but you said
          5 ll. + 1
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [July 4, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 6-o)
          [n.p.] My dearest Alfred I wrote some days ago to Broden/bach
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- July [8, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-a)
          Drei Reichs Kronen My dearest Alfred - The weather is really irri-/tating not for me
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- July 17 [1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-b)
          [Germany] My dearest Margaret How we have pleased ourselves/with writing
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [July 24, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-c)
          Dusseldorf My darling Alfred I have been expec-/ting a letter from you
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [July 26, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-d)
          [n.p.] Dearest darling Alfred I am so glad you/got my letter so quickly
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Aug. 24 [1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-e)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred I am getting so very/anxious to hear from you
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Aug. 30, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-f)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred I would much rather/you
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Sept. 6, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-g)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred - Never any thing did/me so much good
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Oct. 1?, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-h)
          Kensington My dearest Margaret I am so disappointed by/finding no letter from my sister.
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Oct. 16, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-i)
          [n.p.] My own darling Alfred You must think/nothing but that I love/you
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Nov. 27, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-j)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I have sold the upright
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Dec. 6, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-k)
          AL [frag.] S [init.] to [Margaret Raine Hunt]
          [n.p.] ...high in the world
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Dec. 15, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-l)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret What an awful dearth of
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Dec. 17, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-m)
          [Durham] My own dearest Alfred - It is such a pleasure/when the day
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Dec. 23 [1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-n)
          [Durham] My own dearest Alfred No letter you naughty/little thing this morning
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- [Dec. 28, 1860] (Box 1, Folder 7-o)
          [n.p.] My dearest Alfred - I fully expected/ Saturday -
        - Hunt, Margaret Raine, 1831-1912. -- Jan. 6 [1861] (Box 2, Folder 1-a)
          ALS to Alfred Hunt
          [n.p.] My dearest Alfred Your letter was most/welcome
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Jan. 9, 1861] (Box 2, Folder 1-b)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret Mr. Plint has kept the ober-/wesel
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- Jan. 14, 1861 (Box 2, Folder 1-c)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I did send five drawings to
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Jan. 23, 1861] (Box 2, Folder 1-d)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret I saw what I thought/a good opportunity yesterday
        - Hunt, Alfred William, 1830-1896. -- [Jan. 28, 1861] (Box 2, Folder 1-e)
          [Liverpool] My dearest Margaret If you have not done/anything
      - ii. General
        - AL [frag.] to Alfred Hunt -- June 1, 1886 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          The Grobe, Harborne My dear Hunt I have a note from/ Mrs Hunt telling me
        - Empty envelope addressed to Alfred William Hunt -- June 10, 1878 (Box 2, Folder 3-a)
          London
        - [Darlington] -- July 20, 1856 (Box 2, Folder 3-b)
          Empty envelope addressed to Margaret Raine Hunt
          Addressed to Miss Raine.
        - Benson, Venice Hunt, 1864- -- Jan. 18 [n.y.] and [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 4)
          4 ALS to Margaret Raine Hunt
          7 ll.
        - Brett, John, 1831-1902. -- Jan. 17, 1888 (Box 2, Folder 5)
          ALS to Alfred William Hunt
          Atheneum Club, Pall Mall My dear Hunt we had a great scuffle for/you this evening,
        - Browning, Elizabeth Barrett, 1806-1861. -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 6)
          Cara? I send the first volume of Pendennis.
          Handwritten copy by Margaret Raine Hunt, with note containing additional information about the letter.
        - Browning, Florence -- Apr. 23 [1891] (Box 2, Folder 7-a)
          18 De Vere Gardens, W. Dear Mrs. Hunt, I enclose you/a little note
          2 ll. + 2
          With envelope and handwritten copy of letter by Margaret Raine Hunt.
        - Browning, Robert, 1812-1889. -- [Jan. 3, 1882] (Box 2, Folder 7-b)
          19, Warwick Crescent, W. Dear Mrs. Hunt, I was very sorry/to find
        - Browning, Robert, 1812-1889. -- Apr. 29, 1866 (Box 2, Folder 7-c)
          AL [copy] to [Alfred William Hunt?]
          19 Warwick Crescent, W. My dear Sir I made
          use yesterday of the ticket
          Handwritten copy by Margaret Raine Hunt.
        - Browning, Sarianna -- Aug. 27 [1886] (Box 2, Folder 7-d)
          Llangollen, North Wales Dear Mrs. Hunt, Very many thanks/for your kind remem-/brance
        - Browning, Sarianna -- May 8, 1896 (Box 2, Folder 7-e)
          Asolo, Veneto Dear Mrs. Hunt, It is so long since
        - Fleming, Albert -- Nov. 22, 1887 (Box 2, Folder 8)
          Broxbourne, Hertshire Dear Mrs Hunt, If you go into/Mr. Ruskin's affairs at all
          2-ll. + 1
          The letters mentioned in Fleming's letter (not enclosed, as letter indicates) are by ?.
        - Fogg-Elliot, John -- Sept. 30, 1865 (Box 2, Folder 9)
          ALS to Annie [Peacock?]
          Elvet Hill [Durham] My dear Annie We have sold a part
          John Fogg-Elliot married Mary Peacock.
        - Greenwell, Dora, 1821-1882. -- [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 10)
          [n.p.] My dear Margaret, I have/sent the enclosed,
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- Feb. 27 [1857] (Box 2, Folder 11-a)
          Durham My dear Hunt, I hear from/Robinson
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 11-b)
          [n.p.] My dearest Margaret This letter is/merely provisional
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 11-c)
          [n.p.] My dearest Margaret I must put/off having any explanation
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 11-d)
          [n.p.] My dearest Margaret By one of those/unhappy contretemps
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 11-e)
          Marlborough My dearest Margaret Your letter, which/by the way,
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- Thursday [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 11-f)
          Coldshean? My dearest Margaret I ? to Derwent/late because I did not get/your letter
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- Saturday night [n.d.] (Box 2, Folder 11-g)
          [n.p.] My dear Margaret I was so disappointed/not to see you today,
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- Feb. 21 [n.y.] (Box 2, Folder 11-h)
          Brandon My dear Margaret I am on my travels
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- July 21 [n.y.] (Box 2, Folder 11-i)
          Durham My dearest Margaret I must have/the photograph.
        - Greenwell, William, 1820-1918. -- Apr. 8, 1859 (Box 2, Folder 11-j)
          Sprouston, Kelso My dearest Margaret Until Kingsley/wrote to me yesterday I
        - Hodson, S[amuel] J. -- Apr. 4, 1892 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          7 Hillmarton Road, N. Dear Mr Hunt I rely upon your/sending me at least
        - Hook, James Clarke, 1819-1907. -- [n.d., 1867-1886] (Box 2, Folder 13-a-s)